Colorado Springs, CO (760) 525-3768

justinvittitoe7@gmail.com linkedin.com/in/justinvittitoe

I am a dedicated professional with expertise in financial management, data analysis, and business operations. My background includes a Bachelor of Science in Financial Management and experience in financial computing, real estate development, and project management. I excel in problem-solving, improving business processes, and optimizing resources.

KEY SKILLS

Operations | Automation | Pricing Analysis | Customer Service | Quality Assurance | Customer Relationships | Active Listening | Adaptability | Microsoft Office | HTML – CSS - JavaScript | Node.js – Express.js | PostgreSQL | MS Power Automate

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

Mayberry Communities LLC, Operations Specialist

February 2024 – Current

As an Operations Specialist in the new home building industry, I streamline processes, manage contracts, and optimize workflows to enhance efficiency. Oversee new purchase contracts, warranty management, and closing coordination, ensuring seamless transactions for homebuyers, lenders, and internal teams. My customer-first approach allows me to implement solutions that drive operational success.

- Developed and automated the internal and customer-facing documentation process for new home purchases.
- Built and implemented a structured warranty management system within the company's construction software
 ensuring swift attention to homeowner claims to maximize satisfaction.
- Streamlined home closings, ensuring all required documents are processed efficiently with lenders and title companies.
- Expertise in automation tools like Power Automate and Zapier to enhance workflow efficiency.
- Strong skills in problem-solving, leadership, time management, and customer-focused solutions.

Student Managed Portfolio Project

September 2023 - June 2024

Analyst

Successfully grew market share for the bone growth stimulators, pain medication and back bracing. Call points consisted of orthopedic surgeons, neurosurgeons, hand surgeons, and podiatrists.

- Using FactSet to code a filter to find financial liquid firms which follow our prospectus.
- Designed a prospectus explaining the dividend achiever strategy intended to emulate.
- Acquiring and Analyzing data from firms' financial statements to create DDM and FCF models to find a target price.
- Traded covered call options to increase cash flow and to hedge our positions from market shocks.

Ads's Fish House Busser/Server

January 2023 - June 2024

- Maintained an organized work environment to efficiently manage the flow of guests within the restaurant.
- Enhanced customer satisfaction by implementing effective routines to streamline operations and maximize efficiency.
- Consistently maintained an efficient pace of work to accommodate a steady flow of customers while providing excellent service.

Savon Pavers

Field Supervisor

June 2019 - August 2023

- Professional learning experience during a major economic fluctuation, pre-pandemic to post-pandemic.
- Oversaw multiple job sites and manage project development throughout all stages, from demolition to final polishing.
- Communicated and coordinated with customers and supervisors to ensure smooth progress and meet project expectations.

EDUCATION

Bachelor of Science (BS) Financial Management
Business Administration
California Polytechnic University, San Luis Obispo
EdX – Software Engineering Bootcamp